♪ MTV ♪
You have been tasked
to bring justice to a murderer!
But the murderer is you.
Life hasn't shown
me many reasons
to keep fighting for it.
If you don't live.
someday they won't remember
we were even here.
We journey the path
of the pioneers
in the name of lost
love soon to be found.
Hillary. where did he...?
Spencer's coming home.
Get to the train station.
If this Spencer
Dutton steps off.
put a hole in him.
After you've killed the nephew.
we kill the whole lot of 'em.
Bring him home.
Everyone acts like
he's something special.
With a gun in his hand.
there's no one better.
You don't say.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You'd be a lot more
comfortable inside.
Can't stand that house when
my husband isn't in it.
It's just a big log
prison for my worries.
Understood.
Okay.
I'd feel more comfortable
if you sat inside.
Don't fret. Zane.
I'm still spry
enough to run inside
if the bullets start flying.
He'll arrive today. I reckon.
I've done the math.
Sioux Falls to Rapid City.
Rapid City to Deadwood.
Sheridan. and Billings.
And then home...
Then the fight.
Well. anything worth having
is worth fighting for. Zane.
They don't make women
like you anymore. ma'am.
Yes. they do. It's the
men they make different.
He never came home.
Jack. He never came home.
Sit.
He went to town to meet
his uncle on the train.
Felt Jacob was too shorthanded.
Was he? I don't know.
He's lived to be 80
judging such things.
Don't know why a
25-year-old would think
he knows any better.
That's the boy in
him. Elizabeth.
But he's a married man now.
He doesn't get to make decisions
about his life without asking.
Because the consequences
of those decisions
affect more than just him.
I just pray he's
learned that lesson
before it's burned
into you. my dear.
Now get inside before
you catch your death.
Death is the only thing
you can catch out here.
Thank you.
Who are those guys?
We hired 'em in the fall.
More badges in town
while you healed up
from being shot to shit.
I don't know 'em.
Interviewed 'em with your
wife. They seemed fine.
One of them was
a cop in Chicago.
- Irish?
- Think so.
I don't know.
They all sound the same to me.
Banner?
When did you get home?
I don't know. I was late.
Why are you sitting in the dark?
- I'm not a good man. Ellie.
- Banner.
You've been as good as one can
be with the options you've had.
I don't think I'm
a bad man either.
There are takers in this
world and those who get took.
I just got fed up
with being took.
But I'm not evil.
I-I take no pleasure
in another man's pain.
They pay a man $20 a day to work
the fishing trawlers
out of Portland.
You earn more than that here.
I make it.
I don't earn it.
Dutton has half this
county. half the next one.
No bigger taker in the state.
But the man ain't evil.
Whitfield's evil. Ellie.
Heart black as coal.
Dutton...
he takes.
He don't care if you suffer.
I understand that.
I respect it. even.
Whitfield takes to
make you suffer.
It ain't the taking he wants.
It's the suffering.
I don't beat no women.
Use 'em up.
Kill 'em.
Throw 'em off a cliff
and go find another.
Banner.
What in the world are
you talking about?
I'm a man.
Man's got to look
his son in the eye.
Stand by what he did.
I can't do that here.
Not anymore.
Get packed.
We're leaving.
♪ Bach's "Fugue in
C Major" playing ♪
Ever seen anything like that?
Water from the ceiling?
Corn prices.
wheat prices. whole hogs.
cattle yields.
The newspaper of the West
is a commodity report
and a rumor mill.
I long for the London Times.
We live on an island
of mountains. girls.
Surrounded by an
ocean of prairie.
completely cut off
from the electricity of culture
and thoughtful exchange.
But all that changes today.
Why today?
Because today the
present becomes the past
and the future
becomes the present.
Our little sparrow...
...seems worried a
cat's lurking about.
He's talking to you.
Enjoy the evening?
Parts of it.
Ah. parts.
And other parts?
I did not.
But you see.
the parts you wish would end
magnify the pleasure.
The pain is only for reference.
Yeah.
Lay on the table. Mabel.
That rhymes.
It certainly does.
Lay on the table.
Hmm.
Can't say he didn't deserve it.
Men like him beg
the world to do it.
The world usually obliges.
What do you think?
Ran up on this boy.
they shot it out?
Two different boots.
No boots.
No exit from bullet.
Was a pistol.
Boy had a rifle.
You think this girl...?
Priest.
That is the priest's boot.
You think a priest killed him?
I think a priest killed him.
Priest.
We waiting for a signal?
No signal.
Just start killing. then.
Just start killing.
2:20 arrival.
Anybody else know that?
Well. it ain't no secret.
Jacob. and it damn sure won't be
as soon as the ticket
agent shouts it out.
Filling up in there?
Starting to.
Any strange faces I
should know about?
It's a train station. Jacob.
All the faces are strange.
Everyone looks like travelers.
Everyone so far.
Yeah.
Not everyone.
Three first class to Portland.
Sleeper car?
Shared?
First class. I said.
That's $67.
You don't think I have it.
I love being judged
by half a man as me.
Prepay the meals. sir?
We'll pay as we dine.
Train arrives at 2:20.
Departs at 2:45.
I advise being on
the platform at 1:50.
If it arrives early...
- it leaves early.
- We'll wait.
We're not going anywhere.
Take a seat.
I'll be along.
I've seen some cowardly
camouflage in my life...
...but I don't think
I've seen this.
I'm taking my family
and I'm leaving.
Had enough of this place.
You're under indictment.
Banner. you can't go anywhere.
I can't leave the country.
The judge said nothing
about leaving the state.
So I suppose it's a coincidence
that you picked this
particular day to leave.
You mean the same day
as your nephew arrives?
The great hope?
Maybe he is.
Good for you.
You get to keep your land
for a generation or two.
Whitfield's just
the first. you know?
There's more where he came from.
More of them than me.
And way more than you.
They'll never let him
leave this station. Jacob.
You can take my word for
it or you can learn it.
Let 'em try.
And you can try and
get on that train.
but that ain't
gonna happen either.
You started this thing. Banner.
You don't get to leave it.
I've got a son. Jacob.
What have I been teaching him?
Just so long as
they get to leave.
Can you give me that?
Yeah.
I can give you that.
They won't be just here. Jacob.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
Give me your bundle.
Just here.
That bag never
leaves your sight.
Everything okay?
It will be.
There's gonna be chaos
on that platform. Ellie.
People running and screaming.
And we are gonna walk through
it like we're headed to church
and get on that train.
Don't look up.
Don't look anybody in the eye.
Just walk.
Do you understand?
I think so.
Mom. buffalo!
I heard you the
first time. Tucker.
The whole train heard you.
They've got you outnumbered.
They sure do.
Where are we?
Montana.
Thought all the
buffalo were gone.
Not all of 'em.
There's still some here.
Some in. uh. Wind
Rivers. I hear.
Yellowstone has a
pretty big herd.
You ever hear of Little Bighorn?
See right out there?
Lakota called it the
Battle of the Greasy Grass.
Grass here is so rich in
protein. it feel like grease.
Worst defeat in American
military history.
Wait. Custer lost?
You can't lose any worse.
That's not what
they said in school.
They said Custer was a hero.
That's 'cause schools don't
teach you what happened.
They teach you what they
want you to believe.
And they can teach you that.
you'll believe
anything they tell you.
What's that?
A lion's tooth.
- There's no lions here.
- That's 'cause
it's not from here.
it's from Africa.
Want to trade?
Trade what?
That's a nice knife.
Guy I traded for it says
it's from the revolution.
The war.
Our teachers said
we won that one.
You and I are living
proof of that.
Are you sure your
mother would be okay
with you trading this away?
She don't know I have it.
See. I don't know. I was. um...
I was planning on giving
this to my son one day.
What's his name?
I don't know.
Haven't met him yet.
Don't think you meet him.
I think you got to make him.
All right. Tucker.
that's enough.
Stop bothering the man.
No. no. It's no bother.
What do you say?
I don't know.
Please. Disarm the child.
You got a deal.
That's a good trade.
You got suckered.
Know how many pocket knives
there are in the world?
I bet this is the only lion's
tooth in the whole country.
Yeah. you may be right.
This keeps getting
more interesting.
Shot in his sleep.
Shot by who?
Don't know.
Priest maybe.
Face is burned.
Then stabbed.
Stabbed then shot.
He ran out.
So the girl did this.
Didn't do that.
But she did this.
Quite the coyote. this girl.
These men. they talk of this
girl killing everywhere.
but it was the men
killing in Oklahoma
and the men who killed here.
I don't think the
girl is the problem.
I think that's the problem.
And the problem is gone.
Be that as it may.
we have a warrant.
We have a duty to serve it.
A warrant from a
judge we don't know
in a territory we don't serve.
We didn't ride out here to find
a girl. we rode out
here to find them.
And we found 'em.
And good riddance.
She's above us on the ridge.
Ride around her to the east!
She drew her pistol!
Marshal. do not shoot!
- Marshal. do not fire!
- She's fired at us!
You'll be dead before it
reaches your shoulder.
Seems a silly death for one
who's fought so
hard to avoid it.
Better than your noose.
Quicker. no doubt.
And I've lived in your prisons.
I won't do it again.
I don't choose who gets the
noose or who goes to prison.
That's for a judge to decide.
If you're innocent. he'll
give you a chance to prove it.
Prove how?
Through testimony.
Through witnesses.
What witnesses?
The nuns who raped me?
The priests who beat me and
put me in an oven to cook
because I don't know
how to make soap?
Won't eat maggots.
Won't let them put
their fingers inside me.
And who speaks for me?
Which relative
will they dig from their grave
to speak for me?
- What is she talking about?
- The Indian schools.
I know those schools.
Know those priests.
I don't know her path.
But I know that path.
They lied?
You never killed?
The one who beat me I killed.
And the one who
raped me I killed.
Then I killed the one
who murdered my cousin.
Tried to murder me.
Then the priest.
Yes.
I've killed.
I'd say.
What about him?
Badge and boots.
I've been shot.
You ain't been shot.
You been woke up.
Now stay that way.
You son of a bitch.
I'm gonna box you silly
when we get back...
- They're coming.
- Yes.
I know.
Take that shotgun.
Get in the conversation pit.
Stay away from the
windows. get low.
Under the table.
They're here.
There's a whole lot of 'em.
Zane! What do I do?!
You get up high. give us cover.
and use Jacob's elk rifle.
Stay there. you hear me?
Don't shoot me!
Where's Sam?
How many is there?
Don't know. A bunch.
Let 'em get close.
shoot into the cabs.
shoot the drivers. then we get
back to the house and
we fight 'em from there.
Steady.
Not yet.
They're almost on top of us.
Not yet!
Jasper. you take the lead car.
Randy. you get the second car.
Dennis the third.
I get the last.
Get ready.
Kill 'em.
Dennis. you and Randy
get to the house
and get on the roof!
Two can't hold 'em.
Ain't trying to hold 'em.
just trying to slow 'em down.
Go!
What can I do?
You can hide in the basement
with your children. ma'am.
Ma'am. go find your children!
You too. ma'am.
I'm staying here.
Go to the basement!
Lord. help us.
Of all the things I've had
to do for this ranch...
...this takes the cake.
Takes the bloody cake.
25 minute alert for 2:20
from Sheridan. Deadwood.
Pierre. Sioux Falls.
They're here.
How many?
About a dozen.
Plus Banner.
Plus whoever we
haven't picked out yet.
Better get Livingston
Police out here.
There's only three. and
they ain't worth a shit.
Well. that's better
than nothing.
We're gonna stop it
before it comes to that.
This is the only
way we stop them.
What's in Portland?
Your future.
I don't have one here?
A man can't get rich in Montana.
He gets rich somewhere else.
Then he comes to Montana.
And he gets even richer.
I'm sorry. Spencer.
This is your plan?
This is your plan for us?
Let us know love.
then rip it from us...
...then give us a child...
...then drag me
through hell
to freeze here?
Hours from him?
What kind of God does that?
Stop!
Livingston.
This is Seven Pierre 91.
Please!
Please. stop!
Please! Stop!
Alex?
Sir?
Alex!
Spencer?
Spencer!
Alex!
What...?
What are you...?
You sent smoke
signals to my train.
You leapt from the train?
I leapt from the train.
Did you. by chance. ask
the train to wait for us?
No. it slipped my mind.
So. train is continuing
in the opposite direction.
Yeah. that's a
pretty good guess.
Ah. Well...
so good of you to join
me in this pickle.
Free from the burden
of a solution.
I don't know what that means.
It's an insult. my love.
I have a solution.
I'm all ears.
Big Timber's three
miles from here.
I'm gonna carry you.
Carry me?
I've carried an elk
quarter farther.
I don't know what
an elk quarter is.
but I assume very heavy and a
testament to your swarthiness.
Heavier than you.
but not by much.
You've eaten well on
this journey. my love.
You may carry me from
certain death. sir.
but you may not joke about
my weight while doing it.
Hmm.
It's your fault. you know.
My fault?
I suppose he'll
be tall like you.
Huh.
Ow.
I know. I know.
I know.
This is a doctor
traveling in first class.
My name is Andrew.
Open your mouth for me. please.
I need warm water and
towels. lots of it. fast.
I need everyone to
clear the room. please.
And close the door.
There isn't much
medical research
on cold as a clinical condition.
but in the army we saw plenty.
and what we learned is.
if you get cold
fast. you warm fast.
if you get cold slow. you
must warm yourself slowly.
How long were you
exposed to the elements?
I think...
about a-a day or two?
These clothes are
as cold as she is.
We need to get them
off. I apologize.
There's no time for modesty.
There you go.
What do we do about the shivers?
The shiver is good.
It's her body trying to warm.
Was she shivering
when you found her?
Was she disoriented?
- Disoriented how?
- Saying things
that are illogical
or don't make sense.
Oh. she does that anyway.
I can hear you.
Is there any other symptoms?
Her temperature is 94.2 degrees.
She was minutes away from
death when you found her.
Press that tight against her.
All over. sir. don't be bashful.
He has flaws.
but bashful isn't one of them.
Have you two met?
My husband. sir.
It's a long story.
One worth hearing. no doubt.
Put this under her arms.
You must tell us
when the towels cool
so we may replace them.
How many months?
Six.
Will.. will he survive?
We'll see.
The female form is a miracle
that can withstand physical
hardships well beyond
that of men...
especially when with child.
If there is a way to
protect the child.
your body will find it.
I'll be right back.
My... b-body's a miracle.
Hear that?
- I already knew that.
- Hmm.
I never thought
I'd see you again.
You didn't have to
go through all this.
I was coming for you.
Couldn't take the chance.
If you found someone else. how
could I kill her from England?
That rarest of creatures.
Your smile.
I want you to sit
up and drink this.
Slowly.
Slow.
It's likely she's dehydrated
on top of everything else.
Don't get off in Livingston.
Engine man has radioed
the station in Bozeman.
An ambulance is waiting.
They'll take you to the
hospital where they have seen
far more ailments from
the cold than I have.
Let's change out these towels.
Retreat!
Let's get on the roof.
See where they went?
Just down the hill.
They're not going
anywhere till tonight.
I think that's their plan.
Jacob should be back by
then with the sheriff
and everybody else.
We don't know what
they ran into.
They could be in the same boat.
We need someone in the
house with the women.
You're the one with a wife
in there. We got the roof.
Be safe.
And here I thought it
was them boys on the roof
- making lucky shots.
- It was me with the luck.
Though this contraption takes
most of the luck out of it.
They're gonna wait till night.
My guess is try to burn us out.
How do we fight that?
Well. we got a full
moon in our favor.
Just need them clouds to break.
So. we need God to do his part.
We need wind.
I don't care who does
their part to send it.
That would be God.
I'll ask.
If they do get in
the house. Cara...
Just pray for wind
and a bright moon.
I'll ask for wind.
I'll pray my husband comes
and brings Spencer with him.
It's late.
Yep.
Here she comes.
96.8.
- Alex. what?
- Feeling
is coming back to her feet.
That's a new sensation.
Are we there?
Close. It's another
30 miles or so.
Remember what I said.
Ignore the chaos.
get on the train.
Where are you going?
There's enough money in
your bag to start over.
- Start clean.
- Start ov...
What are you talking
about? What's happening?
Trust me.
Clear away!
Clear away for
passengers to disembark.
- Spencer?
- Sir. what are you doing?
Drop it!
Drop it now!
- You drop it.
- Drop it!
Put that gun down.
for God's sakes!
Drop it! Drop them!
Henry.
Ellie!
Get on the train!
So you're a man of
your word after all.
I told you.
Get my family to Portland.
Where they're clean of this.
Clean of me.
You have my word.
It's all a man's got.
What was this?
Fear. I suppose. Arrogance.
Dear God.
You're shot. sir.
Old leaks. I think.
Looks fresh to me.
Bill!
Can you walk?
- Haven't tried.
- Carl!
Give him a hand.
I urge you. take this
train to Bozeman.
There is an ambulance waiting.
- Arrange more...
- We need to load passengers.
- Come back for them.
- It's not as easy as...
Come back for them.
This fight ain't over.
And I ain't got that
much fight left in me.
I need to get my
wife to a hospital.
I'll head home once she's there.
You might not have
a home by then.
Come with me.
This is my uncle.
Jacob.
Ma'am.
War isn't a metaphor in this
family. I'm discovering.
It is not.
Time to fight yours.
I suppose.
If we want a life here. it is.
But we can build
a life anywhere.
This is why she wrote you.
War is what you came home for.
I love you.
I'll meet you in Bozeman.
Let's take a look
at these wounds.
I got a funny feeling
you got quite a story to tell.
Yes.
I could use that.
I need to deputize you.
Taking cars or horses?
Got both. Cars are faster.
In her heart. she feared
she'd never see him again.
But she saw him.
Tasted him one last time.
For her. that was enough.
Ought to trade that
out for a shotgun.
Tricky to shoot around
corners with an elephant gun.
Don't shoot around
corners with this one.
You shoot through them.
Come on.
Show yourself.
Told you not to stay there.
Pretty glad you did.
But don't do it no
more. Get upstairs.
Today is the dawn
of Montana's own Gilded Age.
Today. we begin extracting
the only resource
which increases in value
the more common it becomes...
...tourism.
As farmers abandon the
field for the comfort
and opportunities of the city.
the wilds of America
will become parks.
Playgrounds for the elite.
Let's say they come.
How do we profit? Hotels?
- Yes.
- Restaurants?
- Absolutely.
- And this resort.
the ski resort?
I'm in the final negotiations
- on that property as we speak.
- Inns and cafés
are notoriously
poor business models
and frankly. sir. beneath you.
- Beneath all of us.
- You are correct.
Independently.
But combined.
one place where every whim
of the patron is met...
lodging. dining.
liquor. dancing.
gambling. skiing. hunting...
all of them.
including transportation here
and home. provided by us.
- What about competition?
- Our competition
is Colorado.
Another 600 miles away.
Cities give one
culture. convenience.
but they rob man
of the thing that makes him man:
his insatiable.
inexplicable need
to traverse untamed land.
Battle its monsters.
overcome its mountains.
No concert in
Manhattan can compare.
When you bed a woman.
it is the animal
in you doing it.
That animal needs to wander.
We will give it the chance.
Hear. hear!
- I'll ride with her.
- We have an ambulance
- over here for...
- I said I'm gonna ride with her.
This one's full.
sir. Take another.
- I'll ride in the back.
- I ride in the back.
Not tonight.
How far to the hospital?
Five or six miles.
Would you mind checking
that we have sufficient
fuel for such a journey?
We're not gonna run out of gas.
I've never heard a woman
ask that question before.
Well...
Once bitten. twice shy. Jacob.
Yeah.
Stop the car.
Turn off the engine.
That's coming from
up at the house.
Sounds like it.
Turn off your headlights.
Drive us up the road.
Damn it! They're
gonna need us inside!
- That ain't all of them!
- Stay on the roof.
Keep shooting.
Cara.
They're right outside the house.
Damn this man.
Wait.
Stop the car.
It's Spencer.
Ma'am?
Spencer's here.
Ah.
Aunt Cara?
Spencer?
So you know. I'm
right over here.
I see you. You shot?
No more than anyone else.
Oh.
Oh...
Dang it. Spencer. I didn't
even get to fire a shot.
- Where's Jacob?
- He's at the hospital.
With my wife.
You-you have a wife?
Boy. do I.
I'm in her debt.
Not there for Jacob.
She's got her own problems.
I'll ready the carriage.
We have cars. ma'am.
I don't see him.
Where is he?
- Where's Jack?
- I don't know.
Ma'am. we haven't seen him.
Dennis. take Jasper. ride
the road to Livingston.
Find my boy.
Yes. ma'am.
Which one's the leader?
The leader sits in a mansion.
Destroying lives
while getting fat
and throwing dinner
parties for the men
who will carve this
place to pieces.
He did this?
Most certainly.
What's his name?
Whitfield.
Can't seem to...
find the bullet.
Can't find the
bullet. you idiot.
'cause there is no bullet.
- It's an old wound.
- If the lead
is inside you. it can
poison you slowly.
Do you think I care
about the slow ones?
I'm 80 fucking years old.
Sew it up!
She's dilated over
eight centimeters.
Her body's terminating
the pregnancy.
We should abort and amputate.
You will do nothing of the sort.
Miss. the baby is
six months. if that.
It can't survive
outside the womb.
Your legs are
necrotic to the shin.
Your left hand is
necrotic above the wrist.
You will not see
tomorrow's sunset
if we don't amputate
immediately.
She's crowning.
Let's get this over with.
then move her to surgery.
Bring him to me.
Why are you so
confident it's a boy?
Because I know.
Your guess is correct.
Miss. it's best not
to become attached.
Its lungs are not developed
enough to survive the hour.
much less...
So be it.
Give me the hour.
I need you prepped for surgery.
Give her the goddamn baby.
Hi.
No crueler thing than hope.
Let's prep her for surgery.
No.
- She said no.
- She will die.
and the baby will die.
She can make more children.
She said no.
I'll send a priest.
I don't need one
of those. either.
I'm going to name him John.
After his brother.
He'd like that.
But...
...he'd like a world
you're still in more.
The mother that would choose
herself over her child...
...is no mother at all.
How can I raise a child with
stubs for feet
and clubs for hands?
Then there's two children.
This is a conversation you
should have with your husband.
I think all our
conversations are over.
They were splendid.
In truth. I did
most of the talking.
You tell him why for me.
You tell him yourself.
Well. that's the plan. but...
You can see how well my
plans are working out.
You will tell him yourself.
But his horse was
loose at the house.
No saddle.
Maybe he took a different
horse. his got loose.
We need to go back
for the wagon.
This one?
She's in there.
They wanted
to take my legs and...
...and my hand.
And take our baby...
...throw them all
away like... rubbish.
I said no.
I can see that.
Your legs are a long
way from your heart.
I'm not a dreamer.
I don't imagine...
running through fields.
I have to do it.
And I would never trade...
...what we made...
...for me.
Be patient with him. Spencer.
If he's anything like me...
...he'll be a terrible child.
I wish I could have met her.
Hmm.
You would have liked her.
Mustang wild.
Like somebody else I know.
Now you're talking
about yourself again.
Go to the sale barn.
We need two milk goats.
- Barn ain't open.
- Well. when it does.
you'll be first in line.
And make sure they're
producing now.
Milk next week does us no good.
Do you think I-I could just...
I'm sure they
wouldn't mind. honey.
Perhaps tomorrow.
Cara?
I don't know what to do.
You're not supposed to. my dear.
But I do.
Let's go.
I want to meet the man
who killed my wife.
What business do
you have here...
Lindy?
We talked about this.
Sorry. Sometimes I
just get carried away.
Self-control. Lindy.
is the cornerstone...
Look at me.
You like it here?
Then I think you should leave.
What did I tell you?
Now I understand.
The prodigal son has returned.
Mm-hmm. And he will be the
last thing you ever see.
I suppose you've
a plan for explaining
the murder of a man
in his dining room.
I think we about
killed everybody
we'd have to explain it to.
You took an oath.
That badge came with an oath.
To uphold the law.
The law.
So be it.
To jail we go.
I didn't say stand.
You can't get away with this.
I don't plan to.
I plan on making such an example
of you that it'll be 50 years
before one of your kind dares
enter this valley again.
I want them teaching about
how you died in schoolbooks.
Look at me.
You killed my wife.
I don't know you.
Her name was Alex.
And I would really like
to hear you say it.
Alex?
Next before the court.
United States v.
Teonna Rainwater.
Three counts of murder
at the Indian School
in North Dakota.
Why is this girl in my court
and not before the
North Dakota magistrate?
We spoke with the
magistrate in North Dakota
and he stated all
witnesses in this case
were in the Oklahoma territory.
thus making it more expedient
for the trial be held here.
Are these witnesses present?
If it please the court...
...these are death
certificates for the witnesses:
a Father Jaques Renaud...
...and U.S. Deputy
Marshal Nathan Kent.
So?
Is she charged with
those deaths as well?
No. Your Honor. Their
deaths are unrelated.
We have U.S. Marshal Fossett
prepared to testify
to the specifics
of the witnesses' deaths.
if it please the court.
What would please the court
are witnesses to
support a murder charge.
Does prosecution have witnesses?
We do not. Your Honor.
Do you have evidence
that ties the defendant
to these allegations?
We do not. Your Honor.
Then what are we...
Why are we discussing this?
Prosecution would like
to submit a motion to dismiss.
Please.
Motion granted.
And let's make certain the
North Dakota magistrate
keep its business in North
Dakota where it belongs.
Especially if this is
how they conduct it.
What does that mean?
Means you're free to go.
I'm not sure what to do.
Well. we'd sure like
it if you'd leave.
Go where?
How about home?
Not sure I have one.
Maybe it's time
to find a new one.
For deer.
Right.
I'm not sure which way to go.
I hear California.
More Mexican and
Indians than whites.
Fruit on the trees.
game in the hills.
Land of the Chumash.
West.
If you're standing in the
ocean. you went too far.
Thank you.
Teonna!
You were right to fight back.
Maybe.
But it cost me everything.
Always does.
It is likely there are more
unmarked graves in Montana
than those bestowed with marble
and inscriptions that tell
strangers who lay here.
Lovers need no marker.
They know exactly where
their soulmate rests.
Because they put them there.
Hmm.
I swear. boy. we'll
need three goats
before June the way
you're guzzling it down.
I know.
Feels like you're quitting.
But you're not. child.
The reason for you
being here is gone.
I hope you find another
reason in the city.
and it sweeps you off your feet.
and you write me stupid
letters about him.
A man is the last
thing on my mind.
Well. that's a good
lesson for all of us.
Never works out
that way. though.
No. one always creeps in
there and muddles the senses.
Having your senses
muddled now and again...
it's not the worst thing.
I'll write.
That'd be lovely.
Now. I must return my
attention to the future. here.
Because looking at you
is a window to the past.
And the past...
No matter what life
has in store for me.
I'll always love him.
You won't.
You'll love memories until
you make enough new ones.
And then one day. you
won't remember him at all.
And that's all right.
That's fine. that's life.
I'll remember him enough
for the both of us.
There's wild cattle
in the Crazies.
Rough mountains.
I'd rather gather
'em than buy 'em.
You coming?
You know. I think I'm
gonna sit on the porch.
stare at your son...
ponder the meaning of life.
Shit like that.
Be back in a week or so.
I have no doubt.
You're not on the gather.
Sitting this one out.
Retiring. are you?
I am.
So. what's the plan now?
Sit on the porch and
drink yourself silly
so I'm putting two
babies to bed each night?
Something like that.
What was she like?
Alexandra.
If a shooting star could talk.
That's what she was like. honey.
Talking stars.
Can you imagine?
Who'd have thought
there'd be two?
Spencer never remarried.
Took the comfort of a widow
and made another boy...
...refused to marry her.
and one day. the widow was gone.
For Spencer. her
memory didn't fade.
didn't fray at the
edges and didn't dull.
Not one.
Alexandra Dutton was born
on April Fool's Day. 1901.
in Oxfordshire. England.
And laid to rest March 29. 1924.
When old age robbed
him of his memories.
he simply closed his eyes
and dreamed up new ones.
And 45 years later.
my young brother joined her.
Took you long enough.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm